[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Debridement is a medical procedure which is administered in which case?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Infected tissue", "Presence of dead tissue", "Damaged tissue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the 2000 Census, what is the approximate population of The Bronx, New York?", "correct_answer": "1.3 million", "incorrect_answers": ["530,000", "930,000", "130,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The national motto of the Republic of the Fiji Islands is Rerevaka na Kalou ka Doka na Tui. What does this mean?", "correct_answer": "Fear God and honor the Queen", "incorrect_answers": ["God bless our beautiful motherland", "We kneel before you, blessed land", "Hard work comes before prosperity"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was canvas originally made from?", "correct_answer": "Hemp", "incorrect_answers": ["Wool", "Cotton", "Flax"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Due to this, there is almost no atmosphere on the Moon.", "correct_answer": "Weak gravity", "incorrect_answers": ["Lack of oxygen", "Cold temperature", "Excessive sunshine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Smokeys license plate say in the movie Friday?", "correct_answer": "FCK IT", "incorrect_answers": ["Weed", "Friday", "PUF GIVE"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1986 movie was the winner of the Oscar for Best Picture at the 59th Academy Awards in 1987.", "correct_answer": "Platoon", "incorrect_answers": ["The Mission", "A Room with a View", "Children of a Lesser God"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What time of day does the tiger shark usually hunt?", "correct_answer": "Nighttime", "incorrect_answers": ["They hunt at different times throughout the day", "Early morning", "Mid morning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Red Lobster is a U.S. chain of seafood restaurants. Its original name was this.", "correct_answer": "Harbor for Seafood Lovers", "incorrect_answers": ["Lobster Lovers", "Lobster Barbecue", "Red Harbor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does Daniel name the New Boston well after in the movie, There Will Be Blood?", "correct_answer": "Mary Sunday", "incorrect_answers": ["Eli Sunday", "Himself", "H.W Plainview"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All dinosaurs were cold-blooded reptiles.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of all the microbes on Earth, only about this many have been identified.", "correct_answer": "5 %", "incorrect_answers": ["1 %", "2 %", "10 %"]}]